the-web-directory.co.uk 2018-12-28

# The Web Directory - Privacy Policy

This is the web site of The Web Directory

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name, IP address, web browser type and the pages you accessed on our site. The information we collect is used for internal review and is used to improve the content of our Web page. We will not sell or pass your details to any third parties.

With respect to cookies: We do not set any cookies.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we may allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and click stream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of: Google.

For visitors submitting a listing to The Web Directory, we will record their domain, ip address, email address and submitters name. The IP address of all links submitted are also recorded for security purposes. An email may be sent to you to confirm approval or rejection of your listing

As a user, you agree to any information you enter being stored in a database. We may remove, reject or edit listings at our discretion for any reason.

you As we use Paypal to process all payments, we do not store any of your financial information such as credit card information. Paypal allows our visitors to pay in any way they prefer, including through credit cards, bank accounts, buyer credit or account balances, without sharing your financial information.

When required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our web site. We may share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the-web-directory.co.uk terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

Apart from sending an email notification to inform you whether your listing was approved or rejected, we do not send out any other emails. We will never call you, so in the event someone does call you please never pass on your personal information

**You have the right to:**

request access to your personal data (commonly known as a data subject access request). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.

request correction of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.

Request erasure of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing, where we may have processed your information unlawfully or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request. 

Some of the information you have provided may contain personal information (e.g. your home postal or email address). You can check what information we hold on your company and make any updates by contacting us
